<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Tropical -->

  <Cobra.label>cobra</Cobra.label>
  <Cobra.description>A cobra is a large snake with a venomous bite. Cobras can be highly aggressive if provoked or approached. It is better to stay away from these creatures if possible.</Cobra.description>
  <Cobra.tools.1.label>head</Cobra.tools.1.label>

  <Monkey.label>monkey</Monkey.label>
  <Monkey.description>A monkey is a type of small primeape. It can use its curly tail to grab onto tree branches, which leaves its hands free to do other things.</Monkey.description>
  <Monkey.tools.0.label>left fist</Monkey.tools.0.label>
  <Monkey.tools.1.label>right fist</Monkey.tools.1.label>
  <Monkey.tools.3.label>head</Monkey.tools.3.label>

  <Boomalope.label>boomalope</Boomalope.label>
  <Boomalope.description>Engineered for chemical production, the boomalope grows a large sac of volatile chemicals on its back. Though it is weak and fragile for its size, other animals have learned to avoid it because of the huge explosion it produces when it dies.</Boomalope.description>
  <Boomalope.tools.0.label>head</Boomalope.tools.0.label>

  <Lacosdile.label>lacosdile</Lacosdile.label>
  <Lacosdile.description>A lacosdile is a crossbred and genetically manipulated lizard originally created as part of clever fragrance marketing gig. Being herbivorous and barely dangerous made them very common pets. However as the trends passed lacosdiles were soon found flooding the sewage systems, and in desperation were carried off across the galaxy to the furthest reaches of space. As a result the species now flourish on desolate rimworlds, where they have adapted to become omnivorous.</Lacosdile.description>
  <Lacosdile.tools.0.label>left claw</Lacosdile.tools.0.label>
  <Lacosdile.tools.1.label>right claw</Lacosdile.tools.1.label>
  <Lacosdile.tools.3.label>head</Lacosdile.tools.3.label>

  <Okapi.label>霍加皮</Okapi.label>
  <Okapi.description>A giraffid artiodactyl mammal. Okapis are primarily diurnal but may be active for a few hours in darkness. They are essentially solitary, coming together only to breed. Okapis are herbivores, feeding on tree leaves and buds, grasses, ferns, fruits, and fungi. Okapis inhabit canopy forests at altitudes of 500–1,500 m (1,600–4,900 ft). </Okapi.description>
  <Okapi.tools.0.label>left hoof</Okapi.tools.0.label>
  <Okapi.tools.1.label>left hoof</Okapi.tools.1.label>
  <Okapi.tools.2.label>right hoof</Okapi.tools.2.label>
  <Okapi.tools.3.label>right hoof</Okapi.tools.3.label>
  <Okapi.tools.5.label>head</Okapi.tools.5.label>


</LanguageData>