<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Giant -->

  <Elephant.label>elephant</Elephant.label>
  <Elephant.description>An Elephant is the largest unmodified land mammal. It has a pair of long, ivory tusks that can improvise as tools for moving objects or as deadly weapons. It has a long arm-like trunk on its head that can grip and manipulate objects, much like a hand with fingers would.</Elephant.description>
  <Elephant.tools.0.label>tusk</Elephant.tools.0.label>
  <Elephant.tools.1.label>tusk</Elephant.tools.1.label>
  <Elephant.tools.2.label>left foot</Elephant.tools.2.label>
  <Elephant.tools.3.label>right foot</Elephant.tools.3.label>
  <Elephant.tools.4.label>head</Elephant.tools.4.label>

  <Mammoth.label>猛犸象</Mammoth.label>
  <Mammoth.description></Mammoth.description>
  <Mammoth.tools.0.label>tusk</Mammoth.tools.0.label>
  <Mammoth.tools.1.label>tusk</Mammoth.tools.1.label>
  <Mammoth.tools.2.label>left foot</Mammoth.tools.2.label>
  <Mammoth.tools.3.label>right foot</Mammoth.tools.3.label>
  <Mammoth.tools.4.label>head</Mammoth.tools.4.label>

  <Megasloth.label>megasloth</Megasloth.label>
  <Megasloth.description>A type of ground sloth, megasloth are giant, solitary herbivores. Long extinct after being wiped out by the natives of Earth's America continent, the ground sloth was later brought back using advanced cloning and artificial gestators.</Megasloth.description>
  <Megasloth.tools.0.label>left claw</Megasloth.tools.0.label>
  <Megasloth.tools.1.label>right claw</Megasloth.tools.1.label>
  <Megasloth.tools.3.label>head</Megasloth.tools.3.label>

  <Thrumbo.label>thrumbo</Thrumbo.label>
  <Thrumbo.description>A Thrumbo is a gigantic creature of unknown origin. The Thrumbo is gentle by nature, but extremely dangerous when enraged. Its long fur is exceptionally beautiful and treasured, and its razor-sharp horn is very valuable in most markets. Legends say that an old Thrumbo is the wisest creature in the universe - it simply chooses not to speak.</Thrumbo.description>
  <Thrumbo.tools.0.label>horn</Thrumbo.tools.0.label>
  <Thrumbo.tools.1.label>horn</Thrumbo.tools.1.label>
  <Thrumbo.tools.3.label>left foot</Thrumbo.tools.3.label>
  <Thrumbo.tools.4.label>right foot</Thrumbo.tools.4.label>
  <Thrumbo.tools.5.label>head</Thrumbo.tools.5.label>

  <Megabadger.label>大獾</Megabadger.label>
  <Megabadger.description>A truly massive badger - roughly the size of an elephant in adulthood. Megabadgers are incredibly dangerous creatures, with jaws able to bite a fully grown tree to splinters and skin thick enough to stop most bullets. They are not without the characteristic vicious attitude known of smaller badger species. \n\nHaving been known to wipe out entire colonies in the rimworlds, it is advisable under almost all circumstances to completely avoid interaction with megabadgers.</Megabadger.description>
  <Megabadger.tools.0.label>left claw</Megabadger.tools.0.label>
  <Megabadger.tools.1.label>right claw</Megabadger.tools.1.label>
  <Megabadger.tools.3.label>head</Megabadger.tools.3.label>

  <WoolyRhino.label>披毛犀</WoolyRhino.label>
  <WoolyRhino.description>A rhinoceros almost entirely covered in a coarse fur coat, fit for much colder climates than its hairless cousins.</WoolyRhino.description>
  <WoolyRhino.tools.0.label>horn</WoolyRhino.tools.0.label>
  <WoolyRhino.tools.1.label>horn</WoolyRhino.tools.1.label>
  <WoolyRhino.tools.3.label>head</WoolyRhino.tools.3.label>


</LanguageData>