<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Apparello_Chefhatplus.label>首席厨师帽</Apparello_Chefhatplus.label>
  <Apparello_Chefhatplus.description>A hat armed with timers and very basic scent detectors to help anyone cook their meals just right. The chef hat on it is just for declaring the purpose of this headgear。</Apparello_Chefhatplus.description>

  <Apparel_Psymask.label>Psy 防毒面具</Apparel_Psymask.label>
  <Apparel_Psymask.description>The Psy Company's Gasmask has to be their most profiting product of all times. 
	The built in vision sensor technology allows the wearer to operate in the thickest of toxic clouds and more importantly, survive。</Apparel_Psymask.description>

  <Apparello_Docteur.label>外科医生头饰</Apparello_Docteur.label>
  <Apparello_Docteur.description>When fiddling with someone else's vital organs, sanitary equipment is crucial. Wearing these enhances the doctor's sight with the amplifier modules on the goggles. The surgical mask prevents unwanted bacteria entering the vict...patient。</Apparello_Docteur.description>

  <Apparello_Gas.label>防毒面具</Apparello_Gas.label>
  <Apparello_Gas.description>As an unwieldy and cumbersome protection from gas attacks, this gasmask is not commonly used anymore due to more advanced, better alternatives. However, it is still favored by raiders for its intimidating look。</Apparello_Gas.description>

  <Apparello_ViperGas.label>艾力芬特防毒面具</Apparello_ViperGas.label>
  <Apparello_ViperGas.description>The 'Lefant Industries' Gasmask (Or the "Elephant Mask" as it is more commonly known as) was heavily used by the most military outfits, until one very fatal design flaw was found. The air filters would get caught in closing elevator hatches and ladder steps or rungs while descending。</Apparello_ViperGas.description>

  <Apparello_ViperGasTwo.label>艾力芬特全覆式防毒面具</Apparello_ViperGasTwo.label>
  <Apparello_ViperGasTwo.description>The 'Lefant Industries' Gasmask (Or the "Elephant Mask" as it is more commonly known as) was heavily used by the most military outfits, until one very fatal design flaw was found. The air filters would get caught in closing elevator hatches and ladder steps or rungs while descending. This one is hooded! It is pretty warm。</Apparello_ViperGasTwo.description>

  <Apparello_Cyninja.label>战术小队头盔</Apparello_Cyninja.label>
  <Apparello_Cyninja.description>Designed to be used by tactical squads in urban warfare situations, it comes with a pre-installed velocity booster and built-in aiming assist. It does expose the wearer's brain to minimal and totally acceptable levels of radioactivity, which is okay!</Apparello_Cyninja.description>


</LanguageData>