<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Apparello_Furhat.label>Fur Hat</Apparello_Furhat.label>
  <Apparello_Furhat.description>To keep your head warm in cold climates, wear fur! Be warned though that in the right place, the fur wears you!</Apparello_Furhat.description>

  <Apparel_FSFurHat.label>Norbal fur Hat</Apparel_FSFurHat.label>
  <Apparel_FSFurHat.description>A warm hat made of fur.</Apparel_FSFurHat.description>

  <Apparello_Bandal.label>Baseball Cap</Apparello_Bandal.label>
  <Apparello_Bandal.description>A common cap. Perhaps most famous from the age old game where you hit a ball with a stick-like bat and then run home.</Apparello_Bandal.description>

  <Apparello_pieband.label>Bandana</Apparello_pieband.label>
  <Apparello_pieband.description>A rather simple piece of cloth worn on the head. It covers your hair.</Apparello_pieband.description>

  <Apparel_Tuque.label>Fancy Bandana</Apparel_Tuque.label>
  <Apparel_Tuque.description>This bandana is little more than a fancy piece of cloth that is worn on the head. It covers your hair.</Apparel_Tuque.description>

  <Apparello_Fedora.label>Fedora</Apparello_Fedora.label>
  <Apparello_Fedora.description>Nah, see! These hats are often associated with gangsters and government officials, which are both practically the same.</Apparello_Fedora.description>

  <Apparello_Vandal.label>coif</Apparello_Vandal.label>
  <Apparello_Vandal.description>Common coif from middle age. Offers protection from heat and cold.</Apparello_Vandal.description>

  <Apparel_CowboyHat.label>Duellist's Hat</Apparel_CowboyHat.label>
  <Apparel_CowboyHat.description>A well decorated, brimmed hat. A cowboy would want this.</Apparel_CowboyHat.description>

  <Apparel_Kufiya.label>Kufiya</Apparel_Kufiya.label>
  <Apparel_Kufiya.description>A kufiya is a type of square scarf often wrapped around the face and neck. It is commonly used in arid regions as it provides protection from sunburn, dust and sand.</Apparel_Kufiya.description>

  <Apparel_BowlerHat.label>Hard Hat</Apparel_BowlerHat.label>
  <Apparel_BowlerHat.description>Favoured by the construction workers all across the galaxy. These are known to have saved lives of many who fell prey to the infamous falling lunchbox, hammer or brick.</Apparel_BowlerHat.description>

  <Apparello_Chefhat.label>Chef's Hat</Apparello_Chefhat.label>
  <Apparello_Chefhat.description>These iconic chef hats do serve an actual purpose - keeping the hair in check. Finding hair in your soup often means dissatisfied customer.</Apparello_Chefhat.description>

  <Apparello_Tricorn.label>Tricorn</Apparello_Tricorn.label>
  <Apparello_Tricorn.description>The tricorn is long out of fashion. Why anyone would still wear these is strange. Still, they are comfortable to wear.</Apparello_Tricorn.description>

  <Apparello_Sombrero.label>Sombrero</Apparello_Sombrero.label>
  <Apparello_Sombrero.description>Keeps the sun off your eyes during siesta! Ay caramba!</Apparello_Sombrero.description>

  <Apparello_Cardshark.label>Cardshark Hat</Apparello_Cardshark.label>
  <Apparello_Cardshark.description>Stylish, elegant and soft to the touch. Known as the most important part of western attire, especially amongst the card cheats and other slippery individuals.</Apparello_Cardshark.description>

  <Apparel_BeanieCat.label>cat beanie</Apparel_BeanieCat.label>
  <Apparel_BeanieCat.description>A soft tuque with cute kitty ear design. Still fashionable even in winter.</Apparel_BeanieCat.description>


</LanguageData>