<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Apparel_CowboyHat.label>Duellist's Hat</Apparel_CowboyHat.label>
  <Apparel_CowboyHat.description>A well decorated, brimmed hat. A cowboy would want this。</Apparel_CowboyHat.description>

  <Apparel_Kufiya.label>Kufiya</Apparel_Kufiya.label>
  <Apparel_Kufiya.description>A kufiya is a type of square scarf often wrapped around the face and neck. It is commonly used in arid regions as it provides protection from sunburn, dust and sand。</Apparel_Kufiya.description>

  <Apparello_wassupcap.label>Bicorne</Apparello_wassupcap.label>
  <Apparello_wassupcap.description>An awe inspiring hat. Similar to that of a king with a crown, only captains who have a bicorne are acknowledged as the real deal。</Apparello_wassupcap.description>

  <Apparel_BowlerHat.label>Hard Hat</Apparel_BowlerHat.label>
  <Apparel_BowlerHat.description>Favoured by the construction workers all across the galaxy. These are known to have saved lives of many who fell prey to the infamous falling lunchbox, hammer or brick。</Apparel_BowlerHat.description>

  <Apparello_Chefhat.label>Chef's Hat</Apparello_Chefhat.label>
  <Apparello_Chefhat.description>These iconic chef hats do serve an actual purpose - keeping the hair in check. Finding hair in your soup often means dissatisfied customer。</Apparello_Chefhat.description>

  <Apparello_Commissar.label>Peaked Cap</Apparello_Commissar.label>
  <Apparello_Commissar.description>Often seen on military officers, these indigenous alpha mammals of the battlefields tend to be so amazing that their skills rub off on their clothes。</Apparello_Commissar.description>

  <Apparello_Tricorn.label>Tricorn</Apparello_Tricorn.label>
  <Apparello_Tricorn.description>The tricorn is long out of fashion. Why anyone would still wear these is strange. Still, they are comfortable to wear。</Apparello_Tricorn.description>

  <Apparello_Sombrero.label>Sombrero</Apparello_Sombrero.label>
  <Apparello_Sombrero.description>Keeps the sun off your eyes during siesta! Ay caramba!</Apparello_Sombrero.description>

  <Apparello_Cardshark.label>Cardshark Hat</Apparello_Cardshark.label>
  <Apparello_Cardshark.description>Stylish, elegant and soft to the touch. Known as the most important part of western attire, especially amongst the card cheats and other slippery individuals。</Apparello_Cardshark.description>

  <Winter_RHEF.label>Russian Winter Hat</Winter_RHEF.label>
  <Winter_RHEF.description>A Russian winter hat with ear flaps. It can keep your head warm during the coldest of winters。</Winter_RHEF.description>

  <Winter_Cap.label>Winter Cap</Winter_Cap.label>
  <Winter_Cap.description>A snug, fitted winter-worthy cap to keep your head warm in the harsh cold。</Winter_Cap.description>

  <Apparel_BeanieCat.label>cat beanie</Apparel_BeanieCat.label>
  <Apparel_BeanieCat.description>A soft tuque with cute kitty ear design. Still fashionable even in winter。</Apparel_BeanieCat.description>


</LanguageData>