<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Apparello_Hood.label>Syndicate Hood</Apparello_Hood.label>
  <Apparello_Hood.description>Ultimate protection from the wind! The kind of headwear you see worn by shady characters in dark alleys, glaring at you, with gleaming eyes, Ready to stab yo... *gurgle*</Apparello_Hood.description>

  <Apparel_PhaseHelmet.label>Phase Helmet</Apparel_PhaseHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PhaseHelmet.description>Helmet of the Phase armor.</Apparel_PhaseHelmet.description>

  <Interactor_Helmet.label>Interactor Hood</Interactor_Helmet.label>
  <Interactor_Helmet.description>An interactor hood to pair with the interactor cloak.</Interactor_Helmet.description>

  <Apparello_Raz.label>Joywirer's Cap</Apparello_Raz.label>
  <Apparello_Raz.description>Hardened leather and snazzy goggles. It is almost as if you could pilot your way through someone's psyche with this cap equipped!</Apparello_Raz.description>

  <Apparello_Quote.label>War Engineer's Comm-Link</Apparello_Quote.label>
  <Apparello_Quote.description>Often referred to as Redcaps, the war-engineers were in charge of keeping the supply lines up and running. The are stories of one heroic forward scout war-engineer crashlanding on a Tunnelworld during a war in the local star system. Said engineer eventually escaped the planet after somehow managing to activate a nuclear device in the planet's core, which left the planet uninhabitable. 
		It is not known whether his tale of the Tunnelworld being under dictatorship of a powerhungry scientist was true or not. The ramblings about speedrunning through hell with his girlfriend on tow was big blow on his credibility. The only truth in whole story is that the Tunnelworld did indeed blow up!</Apparello_Quote.description>

  <Apparello_Rockman.label>Shuttle Pilot Helm</Apparello_Rockman.label>
  <Apparello_Rockman.description>All the famous shuttle pilots wore one of these, some were more adorned than others. This is one of the more practical and basic ones.</Apparello_Rockman.description>

  <Apparel_PsychicFoilHelmet.label>Psychic Foil Helmet</Apparel_PsychicFoilHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PsychicFoilHelmet.description>A thin helmet containing finely-tuned sheets of psychically-absorptive foil. Reduces the impact of psychic events.</Apparel_PsychicFoilHelmet.description>


</LanguageData>