<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Hats -->

  <Apparel_Bonnet.label>bonnet</Apparel_Bonnet.label>

  <CryptosleepHat.label>Cryptosleep slave hat</CryptosleepHat.label>
  <CryptosleepHat.description>A half-head head-dress designed for extended cryptosleep. You can rest easy knowing your head won't be naked for hundreds or thousands of years while you sleep.</CryptosleepHat.description>


  <!-- Tribal Tech -->

  <Apparel_RagDress.label>ragged dress</Apparel_RagDress.label>
  <Apparel_RagDress.description>A very basic slave outfit made from cloth and can be crafted anywhere. Decrease social standing, but improving work speed and mental threshold.</Apparel_RagDress.description>

  <Apparel_RagDressB.label>ragged tunic</Apparel_RagDressB.label>
  <Apparel_RagDressB.description>A simple servant outfit made from cloth. Decrease social standing, but improving work speed and mental threshold.</Apparel_RagDressB.description>


  <!-- Medieval Tech -->

  <Apparel_TunicPoor.label>poor tunic</Apparel_TunicPoor.label>
  <Apparel_TunicPoor.description>A single piece apparel commonly used by peasants that only consist of leather belt and poorly made tunic. It offer a bit of protection from the cold.</Apparel_TunicPoor.description>

  <Apparel_TunicFine.label>fine tunic</Apparel_TunicFine.label>
  <Apparel_TunicFine.description>A single piece apparel commonly wore by peasant that consist of finely made tunic and leather belt. Offer moderate protection against cold.</Apparel_TunicFine.description>


  <!-- Victorian Tech -->

  <Apparel_VicScullery.label>scullery maid uniform</Apparel_VicScullery.label>
  <Apparel_VicScullery.description>A design from an era of humanity's first industrial revolution. A scullery maid is the lowest-ranked of female servants responsible for washing dishes and doing other menial household chores. 

    The male equivalent is called a hall boy, whose duties were often among the most disagreeable in the house, such as emptying chamber pots for the higher-ranking servants, and cleaning the boots.</Apparel_VicScullery.description>


</LanguageData>