<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Apparel_PowerArmorHelmet.label>Power Armor Helmet</Apparel_PowerArmorHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_PowerArmorHelmet.description>The helmet part of power armor set. It is mostly used by heavy infantry.</Apparel_PowerArmorHelmet.description>

  <SiegearmorHelmet.label>Siege Armor Helmet</SiegearmorHelmet.label>
  <SiegearmorHelmet.description>This is a helmet of the JE-342A7 "Dvergr (Dwarf)" siege armor. A rugged and trustworthy helmet to protect a soft, fleshy head from even the nastiest of enemies.</SiegearmorHelmet.description>

  <CCArmorHelmet.label>Close Combat Helmet</CCArmorHelmet.label>
  <CCArmorHelmet.description>The JE-257A1 "Einherjar" close combat armor is a modified version of "Dvergr" siege armor.  Some of the thick armor plates have been removed so that high powered actuators and fast recharging shields could be installed.</CCArmorHelmet.description>

  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetRecon.label>recon helmet</Apparel_ArmorHelmetRecon.label>
  <Apparel_ArmorHelmetRecon.description>A high-tech armored helmet with a built-in status computer and a protective plate.\n\nArmor like this is often used by imperial scout troops or glitterworld police forces.</Apparel_ArmorHelmetRecon.description>

  <Apparello_Proto.label>PowerMind-Headgear</Apparello_Proto.label>
  <Apparello_Proto.description>A prototype of a very innovative headgear aimed to enhance synaptic reaction rates. It has some very unsavory side effects such as overbearing nervousness, ringing ears, strange background noises and/or voices.</Apparello_Proto.description>

  <Apparello_ProtoFin.label>MindBlast-Headgear</Apparello_ProtoFin.label>
  <Apparello_ProtoFin.description>A very innovative headgear aimed to enhance synaptic reaction rates. It still has some very unsavory side effects although not as bad as before. Placing an advanced AI core on it seemed to work out most of the kinks. Unfortunately, the AI core also amplifies wearer psychic sensitivity, leaving them extremely vulnerable to psychic powers.</Apparello_ProtoFin.description>

  <Apparello_Antsyhat.label>Antis-Headgear</Apparello_Antsyhat.label>
  <Apparello_Antsyhat.description>A very curious piece of technology, the final iteration of the prototype. Negates the awkward effects even further.</Apparello_Antsyhat.description>

  <Apparello_Meffect.label>Enviro-Headgear</Apparello_Meffect.label>
  <Apparello_Meffect.description>Most importantly airtight headgear designed for deep-space explorers to combat the hostile bacteria on uninhabitable planets.</Apparello_Meffect.description>

  <Apparello_Hivehat.label>Hive Helmet</Apparello_Hivehat.label>
  <Apparello_Hivehat.description>Coupled with the Hive armor, the beastly visage of this helmet could very well cause that 'wet trousers' symptom in your foes.</Apparello_Hivehat.description>

  <Apparello_Hivehell.label>Steam Helmet</Apparello_Hivehell.label>
  <Apparello_Hivehell.description>Bulky headgear designed to match the steamhull. For some reason it reminds everyone of a choo choo train, huh.</Apparello_Hivehell.description>

  <Apparello_LPow.label>Light Power Armor Helmet</Apparello_LPow.label>
  <Apparello_LPow.description>A part of powered light armor set, mostly used by light infantry.</Apparello_LPow.description>

  <Apparel_DoomHelmet.label>Doom Helmet</Apparel_DoomHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_DoomHelmet.description>The helmet part of power armor set. It is mostly used by heavy infantry.</Apparel_DoomHelmet.description>

  <Apparel_HellPowerArmorHelmet.label>Hell Helmet</Apparel_HellPowerArmorHelmet.label>
  <Apparel_HellPowerArmorHelmet.description>The helmet part of power armor set. It is mostly used by heavy infantry.</Apparel_HellPowerArmorHelmet.description>

  <Apparello_Meffectwo.label>Meffect-Headgear</Apparello_Meffectwo.label>
  <Apparello_Meffectwo.description>Mostly airtight headgear designed for deep-space explorers to combat the hostile bacteria on uninhabitable planets.</Apparello_Meffectwo.description>


</LanguageData>