<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Apparello_Lederhose.label>Leather Pants</Apparello_Lederhose.label>
  <Apparello_Lederhose.description>These are a pair of leather pants (sometimes even real leather!). The punk wearing these will always feel lucky.</Apparello_Lederhose.description>

  <Norballo_Loincloth.label>Loincloth</Norballo_Loincloth.label>
  <Norballo_Loincloth.description>A tribal loincloth. It covers parts of you, sort of.</Norballo_Loincloth.description>

  <MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders.label>Suspended Trousers</MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders.label>
  <MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders.description>Medieval era pants, they fit awkwardly and are stitched together with clearly visible leather laces. You need a pair of suspenders to keep these up.</MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders.description>

  <MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders_Striped.label>Suspended Striped Trousers</MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders_Striped.label>
  <MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders_Striped.description>Medieval era pants, they fit awkwardly and are stitched together with clearly visible leather laces. You need a pair of suspenders to keep these up. At least they have strips to show the owners originality.</MedievalTimes_Pants_Suspenders_Striped.description>

  <Apparello_Jeans.label>Jeans</Apparello_Jeans.label>
  <Apparello_Jeans.description>Sturdy farmer pants.</Apparello_Jeans.description>

  <Apparello_Suspender.label>Stablehand Trousers</Apparello_Suspender.label>
  <Apparello_Suspender.description>Ain't a chap on earf lookin' as honest as one wearin' these. With these equipped one should feel more comfortable wading through mud and filth and therefore more inclined to get the job done without distractions.</Apparello_Suspender.description>

  <Apparel_Pants.label>Suspender Pants</Apparel_Pants.label>
  <Apparel_Pants.description>A simple set of pants with suspenders that drape over the shoulders to hold the pants up.</Apparel_Pants.description>

  <Apparel_FlakPants.label>flak pants</Apparel_FlakPants.label>
  <Apparel_FlakPants.description>A pair of pants with armor plates sewn in. While it's not as good as solid armor, it offers effective protection against all manner of attacks while remaining quite comfortable.</Apparel_FlakPants.description>

  <Apparello_Holdem.label>Fancy Pants</Apparello_Holdem.label>
  <Apparello_Holdem.description>Fancy Pants are for elegant colonists. Your legs will be the star of the show!</Apparello_Holdem.description>

  <Apparello_Holser.label>Holstered Chaps</Apparello_Holser.label>
  <Apparello_Holser.description>A pair of chaps with holsters. All of the fastest shooters wore these. They usually got shot in the back.</Apparello_Holser.description>


</LanguageData>