<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <WoodLog.label>wood log</WoodLog.label>
  <WoodLog.description>Wood from trees or other fibrous plants. Useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics. A raw stick of wood can be used as a weapon in a pinch. It can be processed into planks or kindling.</WoodLog.description>
  <WoodLog.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>wood log</WoodLog.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <RedWoodLog.label>redwood</RedWoodLog.label>
  <RedWoodLog.description>Wood from redwood and sequoia trees or other fibrous plants. Red, valuable and more fireproof than regular wood. Useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics. A raw stick of wood can be used as a weapon in a pinch.</RedWoodLog.description>
  <RedWoodLog.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>redwood</RedWoodLog.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <WoodPlank.label>wood plank</WoodPlank.label>
  <WoodPlank.description>Wood planks crafted from wood logs. Useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics.</WoodPlank.description>
  <WoodPlank.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>wooden</WoodPlank.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <Bamboo.label>bamboo log</Bamboo.label>
  <Bamboo.description>Bamboo Logs are a type of wood-like grass. It is a fast growing wood alternative that is useful for construction.</Bamboo.description>
  <Bamboo.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>bamboo log</Bamboo.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <BambooPlank.label>bamboo plank</BambooPlank.label>
  <BambooPlank.description>Bamboo Planks are crafted from Bamboo Logs. They are useful for building structures, weapons and even simple prosthetics.</BambooPlank.description>
  <BambooPlank.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>bamboo</BambooPlank.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <RedWoodPlank.label>redwood plank</RedWoodPlank.label>
  <RedWoodPlank.description>Redwood planks crafted from redwood logs. Useful for building structures, weapons, and even simple prosthetics.</RedWoodPlank.description>
  <RedWoodPlank.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>redwood</RedWoodPlank.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <Kindling.label>firewood</Kindling.label>
  <Kindling.description>Firewood is either created by cutting logs, or salvaged from breaking down bushes. It can act as a fuel for various low-tech buildings, including the steam generator. It burns twice as long compared to unprocessed wood.</Kindling.description>
  <Kindling.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>wooden</Kindling.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>


</LanguageData>