<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Plant matter (inedible by people) -->

  <Kibble.label>Kibble</Kibble.label>
  <Kibble.description>Kibble animal feed made from mixed meat and plant sources. Humans can eat it, but they really, really don't like it.</Kibble.description>

  <Pemmican.label>Pemmican</Pemmican.label>
  <Pemmican.description>A preserved mashed mixture of fat and plant food. Tastes bland, but not offensive. It lasts a very long time without refrigeration. Great for traveling.</Pemmican.description>

  <Hay.label>Hay</Hay.label>
  <Hay.description>Hay is nutrient-rich grasses and shoots, harvested and compacted for storage. Hay is for good animal feed, but is inedible for humans.</Hay.description>

  <Silage.label>Silage</Silage.label>
  <Silage.description>Silage is nutrient-rich fermented hay and raw food product suitable for animal feed. The fermentation process preserves the silage and prevents it from rotting.</Silage.description>

  <RawHops.label>Hops</RawHops.label>
  <RawHops.description>Hops are flowers and seed cones of a Hops Plant. They are necessary as a flavoring and preserving agent for brewing Wort.</RawHops.description>

  <PsychoidLeaves.label>psychoid leaves</PsychoidLeaves.label>
  <PsychoidLeaves.description>Raw cut leaves of a psychoid plant.</PsychoidLeaves.description>

  <SmokeleafLeaves.label>smokeleaf leaves</SmokeleafLeaves.label>
  <SmokeleafLeaves.description>Raw cut leaves of a smokeleaf plant. Can be rolled into smokeable joint at a crafting spot.</SmokeleafLeaves.description>

  <NeutroPetals.label>Neutro Flower Petals</NeutroPetals.label>
  <NeutroPetals.description>Beautiful Yellow-Orange Petals from the Neutro Flower. Used to make Neutroamine, a medicine base.</NeutroPetals.description>

  <aloe.label>Aloe Leaves</aloe.label>
  <aloe.description>A bundle of Aloe Leaves from an Aloe Plant. Aloe Leaves are used as a type of natural medicine.</aloe.description>

  <RawCaoutchouc.label>Caoutchouc</RawCaoutchouc.label>
  <RawCaoutchouc.description>Caoutchouc is a natural rubber sap collected from a Hevea Tree. It can be vulcanized to create useful rubber materials.</RawCaoutchouc.description>


</LanguageData>