<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Bionic parts -->

  <PowerArm.label>Power Arm</PowerArm.label>
  <PowerArm.description>Unparalleled strength and dexterity, and with retractable claws. This is the ultimate arm upgrade!</PowerArm.description>

  <BionicHand.label>Bionic Hand</BionicHand.label>
  <BionicHand.description>Allows the user to perform tasks even faster than with regular hands.</BionicHand.description>

  <BionicFoot.label>Bionic Foot</BionicFoot.label>
  <BionicFoot.description>This prosthesis grants faster walking without stumbling all the time.</BionicFoot.description>

  <BionicEar.label>Bionic Ear Implant</BionicEar.label>
  <BionicEar.description>An advanced device that expands upon the basic functions of the ear drum.</BionicEar.description>

  <BionicJaw.label>Bionic Jaw Implant</BionicJaw.label>
  <BionicJaw.description>Aside from a strong set of teeth, this also comes with a voice modulator.</BionicJaw.description>

  <SilentJaw.label>Silent Jaw Implant</SilentJaw.label>
  <SilentJaw.description>This version of the bionic jaw comes without a voice modulator, useful for abrasive patients.</SilentJaw.description>

  <BionicSpine.label>Bionic Spine</BionicSpine.label>
  <BionicSpine.description>This light and impressing device can replace a damaged spine.</BionicSpine.description>

  <BionicEye.label>Bionic Eye</BionicEye.label>
  <BionicEye.description>Advanced piece of technology made not only to fully replace natural eye, but also to give supernatural vision abilities.</BionicEye.description>

  <BionicArm.label>Bionic Arm</BionicArm.label>
  <BionicArm.description>One of the most sophisticated arm replacements. It gives extreme strength to its user.</BionicArm.description>

  <BionicLeg.label>Bionic Leg</BionicLeg.label>
  <BionicLeg.description>A Bionic Leg uses cutting-edge technology to give its owner extreme walking comfort and strength.</BionicLeg.description>

  <PowerClaw.label>Power Claw</PowerClaw.label>
  <PowerClaw.description>A powerful hand replacement consisting of three deadly claws.</PowerClaw.description>

  <ScytherBlade.label>Scyther Blade</ScytherBlade.label>
  <ScytherBlade.description>Hand replacement with a telescoping blade. Scavenged from a dead Scyther Mechanoid. Not very comfortable, but quite effective as a close-range weapon.</ScytherBlade.description>

  <MedicalRib.label>Medical Rib Replacement</MedicalRib.label>
  <MedicalRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little blood filters and antibiotics-dispensers to keep the user healthy.</MedicalRib.description>

  <AdrenalineRib.label>Adrenaline Rib Replacement</AdrenalineRib.label>
  <AdrenalineRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little adrenaline-dispensers to keep the fit and awake.</AdrenalineRib.description>

  <DruggedRib.label>drugged rib replacement</DruggedRib.label>
  <DruggedRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little flake-dispensers to keep the user happy.</DruggedRib.description>

  <BrainStimulator.label>Brain Stimulator</BrainStimulator.label>
  <BrainStimulator.description>A small device that sends electric shocks to the brain to slightly boost consciousness and mobility.</BrainStimulator.description>

  <PainkillerRib.label>painkiller rib replacement</PainkillerRib.label>
  <PainkillerRib.description>An artificial rib, equipped with little morphine-dispensers to numb the user's pain. Side effects are respiratory ailments.</PainkillerRib.description>


</LanguageData>