<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Chemfuel.label>Ethanol Fuel</Chemfuel.label>
  <Chemfuel.description>A can of Ethanol Fuel produced from Wheat, Corn or Rice at a Brewery. It can be used to fuel the Steam Generator. Also can be used to fuel rockets and other machines。</Chemfuel.description>
  <Chemfuel.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>乙醇燃料</Chemfuel.stuffProps.stuffAdjective>

  <BioDiesel.label>生物柴油</BioDiesel.label>
  <BioDiesel.description>A can of BioDiesel Fuel produced from Bean Pods at a BioRefinery. It can be used to fuel the BioGenerator. Also can be used to fuel rockets and other machines。</BioDiesel.description>

  <Powder.label>枪药</Powder.label>
  <Powder.description>Gunpowder, also known as black powder, is the earliest known chemical explosive. It is a mixture of Sulfur, Coal Ore and Nitre. The Sulfur and Coal Ore act as fuels, and the Nitre is an oxidizer。</Powder.description>

  <Napalm.label>凝固汽油</Napalm.label>
  <Napalm.description>Napalm is flammable liquid used in warfare. It is a mixture of a gelling agent and petroleum or a similar fuel。</Napalm.description>

  <Fuel.label>燃料油</Fuel.label>
  <Fuel.description>A type of fuel created from refined Crude Oil. It is needed to power the Fuel Power Plant Also can be used to fuel rockets and other machines.。</Fuel.description>


  <!-- Explosives from CR -->

  <Prometheum.label>普罗米修姆（燃剂）</Prometheum.label>
  <Prometheum.description>Military-grade incendiary agent, ignites on contact with oxygen. The raw resource is used to craft incendiary ammo of all kinds。</Prometheum.description>

  <FSX.label>FSX（燃剂）</FSX.label>
  <FSX.description>High-explosive chemical extracted from Boomalope sacks, it is used in a variety of industrial and military applications。</FSX.description>


  <!--[Core] <Chemfuel.label>化合燃料</Chemfuel.label>-->
  <!--[Core] <Chemfuel.description>挥发性液体化合物。用作火箭和其他机械的燃料。</Chemfuel.description>-->
  <!--<Chemfuel.label>乙醇燃料</Chemfuel.label>-->
  <!--<Chemfuel.description>A can of Ethanol Fuel produced from Wheat, Corn or Rice at a Brewery. It can be used to fuel the Steam Generator. Also can be used to fuel rockets and other machines。</Chemfuel.description>-->

</LanguageData>