<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- cybernetic parts -->

  <GTEar.label>神经电子仿生耳</GTEar.label>
  <GTEar.description>The advanced version of the bionic ear. The second generation of bionic upgrades, typically reserved for top brass military forces。</GTEar.description>

  <GTEye.label>神经电子仿生眼</GTEye.label>
  <GTEye.description>The advanced version of the bionic eye. The second generation of bionic upgrades, typically reserved for top brass military forces。</GTEye.description>

  <GTArm.label>神经电子仿生臂</GTArm.label>
  <GTArm.description>The second generation of bionic upgrades, using nano fibres to produce artificial muscles. Gives the owner incredible strength. You may destroy your opponents limbs in a fist fight...not recomended for wardens。</GTArm.description>

  <CyberneticPowerArm.label>神经电子动力臂</CyberneticPowerArm.label>
  <CyberneticPowerArm.description>Even more unparalleled strength and dexterity, and with a sharp, retractable claws. Now it's the ultimate arm upgrade!</CyberneticPowerArm.description>

  <GTLeg.label>神经电子仿生腿</GTLeg.label>
  <GTLeg.description>The second generation of bionic upgrades, using nano fibres to produce artificial muscles. Give the owner incredible speed</GTLeg.description>

  <GTHeart.label>神经电子仿生心</GTHeart.label>
  <GTHeart.description>A powerful cardiac augmentation, replacing standard human hearts. Safely manages very high blood flow without overwhelming standard body parts。</GTHeart.description>

  <GTLung.label>神经电子仿生肺</GTLung.label>
  <GTLung.description>A powerful vascular augmentation, replacing standard human lungs. The perfect pairing with a cybernetic heart, this increases circulatory speed, increasing efficiency。</GTLung.description>

  <GTKidney.label>神经电子仿生肾</GTKidney.label>
  <GTKidney.description>A powerful abdominal augmentation, replacing standard human kidneys. Increasing blood filtration efficiency。</GTKidney.description>

  <GTLiver.label>神经电子仿生肝</GTLiver.label>
  <GTLiver.description>A powerful abdominal augmentation, replacing standard human livers. Increasing blood filtration efficiency and metabolic efficiency。</GTLiver.description>

  <GTstomach.label>神经电子仿生胃</GTstomach.label>
  <GTstomach.description>A powerful abdominal augmentation, replacing standard human stomachs. Increasing digestion efficiency and metabolic efficiency。</GTstomach.description>

  <GTHand.label>神经电子仿生手</GTHand.label>
  <GTHand.description>The second generation of bionic upgrades, using nano fibres to produce artificial muscles. The more limited version of arm upgrades, just replacing hands。</GTHand.description>

  <GTFoot.label>神经电子仿生足</GTFoot.label>
  <GTFoot.description>The second generation of bionic upgrades, using nano fibres to produce artificial muscles. The more limited version of leg upgrades, just replacing feet。</GTFoot.description>

  <GTDentures.label>神经电子仿生颌</GTDentures.label>
  <GTDentures.description>The second generation of bionic upgrades, using nano machinery to break down food instantly with minimal effort。</GTDentures.description>

  <GTSpine.label>神经电子仿生脊柱</GTSpine.label>
  <GTSpine.description>The most crucial part of the human body improved with the best available nano materials. Greatly imroved manipulation and movement。</GTSpine.description>

  <Exoskeleton.label>外骨骼</Exoskeleton.label>
  <Exoskeleton.description>Greatly improves overall body perfomance。</Exoskeleton.description>


</LanguageData>