<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Plant_Moss.label>moss</Plant_Moss.label>
  <Plant_Moss.description>Wild moss that grows in clumps in areas of low light and cool temperatures. Moss takes a long time to grow, but is very frost-resistant.</Plant_Moss.description>

  <Plant_ShrubLow.label>low shrubs</Plant_ShrubLow.label>
  <Plant_ShrubLow.description>Low broadleaf shrubs. These grow in clusters and slow down movement somewhat.</Plant_ShrubLow.description>

  <Plant_Chokevine.label>chokevine</Plant_Chokevine.label>
  <Plant_Chokevine.description>Dense shrub which slows down anyone moving over it.</Plant_Chokevine.description>

  <Plant_Brambles.label>brambles</Plant_Brambles.label>
  <Plant_Brambles.description>Tangled, thorny, woody shoots covered with leaves. Slows down anyone moving over it a little bit.</Plant_Brambles.description>

  <Plant_Fern.label>fern</Plant_Fern.label>
  <Plant_Fern.description>A soft, leafy plant that reproduces using spores.</Plant_Fern.description>

  <Plant_Bromeliad.label>bromeliad</Plant_Bromeliad.label>
  <Plant_Bromeliad.description>A plant adapted to warm climates. It can grow on thin soil and traps water in its leaves.</Plant_Bromeliad.description>

  <Plant_Hosta.label>hosta</Plant_Hosta.label>
  <Plant_Hosta.description>An attractive shade-tolerant plant.</Plant_Hosta.description>


  <!-- Grass -->

  <Plant_Grass.label>grass</Plant_Grass.label>
  <Plant_Grass.description>Wild grass. It grows anywhere that there is a little light and minimally fertile ground.</Plant_Grass.description>

  <Plant_TallGrass.label>tall grass</Plant_TallGrass.label>
  <Plant_TallGrass.description>Wild tall grass is grass that grew exceedingly high. It significantly slows down anyone moving over it.</Plant_TallGrass.description>

  <Plant_Haygrass.label>haygrass</Plant_Haygrass.label>
  <Plant_Haygrass.description>A mixture of nutrient-rich grasses that yield large amounts of Hay. Hay is edible for animals, but not humans. Haygrass is not destroyed when an animal eats it, so it can be used to make an improved, more compact grazing area for ranching animals.</Plant_Haygrass.description>

  <Plant_WildRose.label>wild rose flowers</Plant_WildRose.label>
  <Plant_WildRose.description>Wild rose flowers are from wild rose seeds and produce red flowers called wild roses. The plant is also known as the prickly rose, bristly rose and arctic rose. They are used in berb collections made from the tobacco rolling bench, Advanced medicine kits made from the medical table, and lastly, into luxury meals from the cook stove.</Plant_WildRose.description>

  <Plant_Hypericum.label>hypericum plant</Plant_Hypericum.label>
  <Plant_Hypericum.description>Hypericum plants produce a type of medicinal flower called hypericum. They are used in herb collections made from the tobacco rolling bench, advanced medicine kits made from the medical table, and lastly, into luxury meals from the cook stove.</Plant_Hypericum.description>

  <Plant_Mint.label>mint plant</Plant_Mint.label>
  <Plant_Mint.description>Mint plants are herbs that grow aromatic leaves called mint leaves. They are used in herb collections made from the tobacco rolling bench, advanced medicine kits made from the medical table, and into luxury meals from the cook stove.</Plant_Mint.description>

  <Plant_Onion.label>onion plant</Plant_Onion.label>
  <Plant_Onion.description>Onions plants produce vegetable bulbs called onions. They are considered to be a luxury crop and are used in Luxury Meals from the Cook Stove. A pungent chemical is released when onions are chopped that can make you cry!</Plant_Onion.description>


</LanguageData>