<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Plant_Agave.label>agave</Plant_Agave.label>
  <Plant_Agave.description>A large-leafed desert plant with edible flowers and stalks.</Plant_Agave.description>

  <Plant_Berry.label>raspberry bush</Plant_Berry.label>
  <Plant_Berry.description>Raspberry bushes are plants that produce fragile, red, bumpy fruits called raspberries.</Plant_Berry.description>

  <Plant_TreeCocoa.label>Cocoa Tree</Plant_TreeCocoa.label>
  <Plant_TreeCocoa.description>Cocoa Trees produce seeds in pods that are called Cocoa Beans. Cocoa Beans can be refined into chocolate.</Plant_TreeCocoa.description>

  <Plant_TreeApple.label>Apple Tree</Plant_TreeApple.label>
  <Plant_TreeApple.description>Apple Trees produce round, palm-sized, red fruits called Apples. The Apple Tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of Apple production.</Plant_TreeApple.description>

  <Plant_TreeBanana.label>Banana Tree</Plant_TreeBanana.label>
  <Plant_TreeBanana.description>Banana Trees produce long, yellow fruits called Bananas, which eventually soften into a sweet delight. The Banana Tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of Banana production.</Plant_TreeBanana.description>

  <Plant_TreeOrange.label>Orange Tree</Plant_TreeOrange.label>
  <Plant_TreeOrange.description>Orange Trees produce sweet, citric fruits called Oranges. The Orange Tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of Orange production.</Plant_TreeOrange.description>

  <Plant_TreePeach.label>peach tree</Plant_TreePeach.label>
  <Plant_TreePeach.description>Peach trees produce soft, fuzzy, sweet fruits called peaches. The peach tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of peach production.</Plant_TreePeach.description>

  <Plant_TreeGrape.label>grape vine</Plant_TreeGrape.label>
  <Plant_TreeGrape.description>Grape vines produce small, sweet berries that grow in clusters on a single branch. These fruits are called grapes.</Plant_TreeGrape.description>


</LanguageData>