<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Decorative -->

  <PlantVenus.label>Venus Flowers</PlantVenus.label>
  <PlantVenus.description></PlantVenus.description>

  <PlantAstragalus.label>Astragalus Flowers</PlantAstragalus.label>
  <PlantAstragalus.description>Astragalus Flowers are small perennial wild flowers that grow in alpine climates. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantAstragalus.description>

  <PlantRose.label>Rose Flowers</PlantRose.label>
  <PlantRose.description>Roses Flowers are red, beautiful cultivated flowers that are symbolic of love and romance since ancient times. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantRose.description>

  <PlantWhiteRose.label>White Rose Flowers</PlantWhiteRose.label>
  <PlantWhiteRose.description>Roses Flowers are white, beautiful cultivated flowers that are symbolic of love and romance since ancient times. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantWhiteRose.description>

  <PlantDaylily.label>Daylily Flowers</PlantDaylily.label>
  <PlantDaylily.description>Daylily Flowers are beautiful, cultivated flowers. They are great for brightening up a drab yard, but must be replanted often. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantDaylily.description>

  <PlantDandelion.label>Dandelion Flowers</PlantDandelion.label>
  <PlantDandelion.description>Dandelion Flowers are common, yellow, small flowers. Though it is often considered a pest weed, it is pleasant to look at. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantDandelion.description>

  <PlantRosebay.label>Rosebay Flowers</PlantRosebay.label>
  <PlantRosebay.description>Rosebay Flowers are small, gorgeous, tough wild flowers that grows in temperate climates. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantRosebay.description>

  <PlantDelphinium.label>Delphinium Flowers</PlantDelphinium.label>
  <PlantDelphinium.description>Delphinium Flowers are elegant cultivated flowers with a majestic purple tint. It has a short lifepsan, so it must be replanted often. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantDelphinium.description>

  <PlantCrocus.label>Crocus Flowers</PlantCrocus.label>
  <PlantCrocus.description>Crocus Flowers are common, small flowers. Though it is often considered a pest weed, it is pleasant to look at. It does not need seeds to be planted, but it does not produce anything except beauty while the flower is alive。</PlantCrocus.description>

  <PlantAnthurium.label>Anthurium</PlantAnthurium.label>
  <PlantAnthurium.description>A beautiful cultivated red flower。</PlantAnthurium.description>


</LanguageData>