<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <PlantAgave.label>agave</PlantAgave.label>
  <PlantAgave.description>A large-leafed desert plant with edible flowers and stalks。</PlantAgave.description>

  <PlantRaspberry.label>raspberry bush</PlantRaspberry.label>
  <PlantRaspberry.description>Raspberry bushes are plants that produce fragile, red, bumpy fruits called raspberries。</PlantRaspberry.description>

  <PlantStrawberry.label>strawberry plant</PlantStrawberry.label>
  <PlantStrawberry.description>Strawberry plants produce small, tasty red fruits called strawberries. These fruits are delicious even when raw。</PlantStrawberry.description>

  <Plantblueberry.label>blueberry bush</Plantblueberry.label>
  <Plantblueberry.description>Blueberry bushes produce tiny, round, blue colored fruits called blueberries. Blueberries are tasty when eaten raw。</Plantblueberry.description>

  <Plantcloudberry.label>cloudberry bush</Plantcloudberry.label>
  <Plantcloudberry.description>Cloudberry bushes produce sweet, amber-coloured, raspberry-shaped fruits called cloudberries. Cloudberry bushes are capable of growing well in cold climates。</Plantcloudberry.description>

  <Plantgooseberry.label>gooseberry bush</Plantgooseberry.label>
  <Plantgooseberry.description>Gooseberry bush produce small, sweet, somewhat hairy fruits called Gooseberries. Gooseberry bushes can grow in cold climates。</Plantgooseberry.description>

  <Plantcocoa.label>Cocoa Tree</Plantcocoa.label>
  <Plantcocoa.description>Cocoa Trees produce seeds in pods that are called Cocoa Beans. Cocoa Beans can be refined into chocolate。</Plantcocoa.description>

  <PlantAppletree.label>Apple Tree</PlantAppletree.label>
  <PlantAppletree.description>Apple Trees produce round, palm-sized, red fruits called Apples. The Apple Tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of Apple production。</PlantAppletree.description>

  <PlantBananaTree.label>Banana Tree</PlantBananaTree.label>
  <PlantBananaTree.description>Banana Trees produce long, yellow fruits called Bananas, which eventually soften into a sweet delight. The Banana Tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of Banana production。</PlantBananaTree.description>

  <PlantorangeTree.label>Orange Tree</PlantorangeTree.label>
  <PlantorangeTree.description>Orange Trees produce sweet, citric fruits called Oranges. The Orange Tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of Orange production。</PlantorangeTree.description>

  <PlantPeachTree.label>peach tree</PlantPeachTree.label>
  <PlantPeachTree.description>Peach trees produce soft, fuzzy, sweet fruits called peaches. The peach tree will remain after harvesting and will start another cycle of peach production。</PlantPeachTree.description>

  <Plantgrape.label>grape vine</Plantgrape.label>
  <Plantgrape.description>Grape vines produce small, sweet berries that grow in clusters on a single branch. These fruits are called grapes。</Plantgrape.description>


</LanguageData>