<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- MOSIN-NAGANT M91 -->

  <RF_Gun_Mosin.label>莫辛-纳甘  M91</RF_Gun_Mosin.label>
  <RF_Gun_Mosin.description>Ancient bolt-action rifle. Probably pulled from a basement somewhere. Good range, Good power, low rate of fire.</RF_Gun_Mosin.description>
  <RF_Gun_Mosin.tools.0.label>stock</RF_Gun_Mosin.tools.0.label>
  <RF_Gun_Mosin.tools.1.label>barrel</RF_Gun_Mosin.tools.1.label>
  <RF_Gun_Mosin.tools.2.label>muzzle</RF_Gun_Mosin.tools.2.label>


  <!-- AKS-74U -->

  <Gun_AKS74U.label>AKS-74U</Gun_AKS74U.label>
  <Gun_AKS74U.description>The AKS-74U short assault rifle (the "U" suffix means"Ukorochennyj" in Russian = "Shortened" in English) has been developed in the late 1970s from the  AKS-74 assault rifle. The AKS-74U was intended as a personal defense weapon for tank, gun, helicopter and other vehicle crews,and for the special operations forces. The AKS-74U has the size and effective range of a typical submachine gun, but has advantage of the assault rifle ammunition and magazines. Average damage and rate of fire, low range, poor accurracy.</Gun_AKS74U.description>
  <Gun_AKS74U.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_AKS74U.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_AKS74U.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_AKS74U.tools.1.label>
  <Gun_AKS74U.tools.2.label>muzzle</Gun_AKS74U.tools.2.label>


  <!-- BERETTA CX4 -->

  <RF_Gun_CXfour.label>贝瑞塔 CX4</RF_Gun_CXfour.label>
  <RF_Gun_CXfour.description>A highly reliable, compact pistol calibre carbine designed to fire pistol rounds up to rifle range. Below average damage, average fire rate, above average range and fires in two round burst.</RF_Gun_CXfour.description>
  <RF_Gun_CXfour.tools.0.label>stock</RF_Gun_CXfour.tools.0.label>
  <RF_Gun_CXfour.tools.1.label>barrel</RF_Gun_CXfour.tools.1.label>
  <RF_Gun_CXfour.tools.2.label>muzzle</RF_Gun_CXfour.tools.2.label>


  <!-- RUGER PC-9 -->

  <RF_Gun_PCnine.label>鲁格 PC-9</RF_Gun_PCnine.label>
  <RF_Gun_PCnine.description>A pistol calibre carbine sidearm carried on the back. Its long barrel allows it to fire pistol bullets at rifle range. Average damage, above average fire rate and range.</RF_Gun_PCnine.description>
  <RF_Gun_PCnine.tools.0.label>stock</RF_Gun_PCnine.tools.0.label>
  <RF_Gun_PCnine.tools.1.label>barrel</RF_Gun_PCnine.tools.1.label>
  <RF_Gun_PCnine.tools.2.label>muzzle</RF_Gun_PCnine.tools.2.label>


  <!-- HK USC -->

  <RF_Gun_USC.label>HK USC</RF_Gun_USC.label>
  <RF_Gun_USC.description>A stable semi-automatic pistol calibre carbine with low kickback and an unusual stock design. Average damage, above average fire rate and range, fires three round bursts.</RF_Gun_USC.description>
  <RF_Gun_USC.tools.0.label>stock</RF_Gun_USC.tools.0.label>
  <RF_Gun_USC.tools.1.label>barrel</RF_Gun_USC.tools.1.label>
  <RF_Gun_USC.tools.2.label>muzzle</RF_Gun_USC.tools.2.label>


  <!-- M4A1 -->

  <Gun_M4A1Gun.label>M4A1 卡宾枪</Gun_M4A1Gun.label>
  <Gun_M4A1Gun.description>The M4 Carbine is a shorter and lighter variant of the M16A2 assault rifle, is heavily used by the United States Armed Forces and is replacing the M16 rifle in most United States Army and United States Marine Corps combat units as the primary infantry weapon. Average damage and range, good rate of fire and accurracy.</Gun_M4A1Gun.description>
  <Gun_M4A1Gun.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_M4A1Gun.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_M4A1Gun.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_M4A1Gun.tools.1.label>
  <Gun_M4A1Gun.tools.2.label>muzzle</Gun_M4A1Gun.tools.2.label>


</LanguageData>