<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Big threats -->

  <RaidEnemy.label>enemy raid</RaidEnemy.label>
  <RaidEnemyDesperate.label>enemy raid</RaidEnemyDesperate.label>


  <!-- More hivePointMultiplier = less total hive count -->

  <Infestation.label>infestation</Infestation.label>
  <Infestation.letterText>Giant insects are tunneling towards you! They will break through in a few seconds and plant hives.\n\nThe hives will spawn more insects and more hives.\n\nIf you don't want the insects to infest the whole area, destroy the hives. But beware - the bugs will defend their home.</Infestation.letterText>
  <Infestation.letterLabel>Infestation</Infestation.letterLabel>

  <DeepDrillInfestation.label>deep drill infestation</DeepDrillInfestation.label>
  <DeepDrillInfestation.letterText>Vibrations from your deep drills have angered some underground insects. Now they're tunneling upwards to seek revenge!\n\nBeware - the insects have been angered and will try to destroy your base.</DeepDrillInfestation.letterText>
  <DeepDrillInfestation.letterLabel>Too deep: Infestation</DeepDrillInfestation.letterLabel>

  <ManhunterPack.label>manhunter pack</ManhunterPack.label>
  <ManhunterPackInfected.label>infected manhunter pack</ManhunterPackInfected.label>

  <DefoliatorShipPartCrash.label>ship part crash (defoliator)</DefoliatorShipPartCrash.label>
  <DefoliatorShipPartCrash.letterText>A large piece of an ancient ship has crashed nearby.\n\nIts mysterious influence will kill all plants in an expanding circle around itself.\n\nDestroy it as soon as possible. But beware - it will probably defend itself.</DefoliatorShipPartCrash.letterText>
  <DefoliatorShipPartCrash.letterLabel>Defoliator ship</DefoliatorShipPartCrash.letterLabel>

  <PsychicEmanatorShipPartCrash.label>ship part crash (psychic)</PsychicEmanatorShipPartCrash.label>
  <PsychicEmanatorShipPartCrash.letterText>A large piece of an ancient ship has crashed nearby.\n\nYour colonists can feel it in the back of their mind, exhorting unspeakable acts. It must have an onboard machine persona with psychic projection ability. And this persona is not friendly.\n\nDestroy it as soon as possible. But beware - it will probably defend itself.</PsychicEmanatorShipPartCrash.letterText>
  <PsychicEmanatorShipPartCrash.letterLabel>Psychic ship</PsychicEmanatorShipPartCrash.letterLabel>

  <AnimalInsanityMass.label>mass animal insanity</AnimalInsanityMass.label>

  <MechCluster.label>mech cluster</MechCluster.label>
  <MechCluster.letterText>A mechanoid combat cluster is landing nearby. The cluster will be initially dormant, so you can take time to decide how to attack it.\n\nIt may remain dormant until disturbed, or it may have a timer or proximity activators.\n\nEven dormant mech clusters aren't harmless. A dormant cluster may assemble mechanoid attackers from time to time, or have some broader negative effect that must be dealt with eventually.</MechCluster.letterText>
  <MechCluster.letterLabel>Mechanoid cluster</MechCluster.letterLabel>


  <!-- Small threats -->

  <AnimalInsanitySingle.label>single animal insanity</AnimalInsanitySingle.label>


</LanguageData>