<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Power -->

  <SK_Power.label>电力</SK_Power.label>
  <SK_Power.description>Learn the basics of power generation to help your colonists survive in this harsh climate.  This advancement unlocks conduits and batteries。</SK_Power.description>


  <!-- PowerConduit -->

  <SK_RenewableI.label>可再生能源 I</SK_RenewableI.label>
  <SK_RenewableI.description>Learn the basics of power generation from renewable resourses of this planet. This advancement unlocks Wind Turbine。</SK_RenewableI.description>


  <!-- WindTurbine -->

  <SolarPanels.label>可再生能源 II</SolarPanels.label>
  <SolarPanels.description>Further advancements in power technology, give your colonists the ability to harness the power of the sun.  Unlocks the solar powered generator。</SolarPanels.description>


  <!-- SolarGenerator -->

  <GeothermalPower.label>可再生能源 III</GeothermalPower.label>
  <GeothermalPower.description>What do you do when the sun doesn't shine?  Solar power is great, except when it's dark!  This advancement in power generation unlocks the geothermal generator that can harness the power of the planet!</GeothermalPower.description>


  <!-- GeothermalGenerator -->

  <SK_RenewableIV.label>可再生能源 IV</SK_RenewableIV.label>
  <SK_RenewableIV.description>Allows to build advanced power plants: Gauss wind turbine and thermoelectric generator。</SK_RenewableIV.description>


  <!-- Adv SolarGenerator
								Adv WindTurbine -->

  <SK_RenewableV.label>可再生能源 V</SK_RenewableV.label>
  <SK_RenewableV.description>Allows to build advanced power plants: Gauss wind turbine and thermoelectric generator。</SK_RenewableV.description>


  <!-- GauseWindTurbine
										ThermoelectricGenerator -->

  <SK_ConvectionalI.label>Conventional power I</SK_ConvectionalI.label>
  <SK_ConvectionalI.description>Learn the basics of power generation from conventional resources of this planet. This advancement unlocks Steam Generator。</SK_ConvectionalI.description>


  <!-- SteamGenerator -->

  <SK_ConvectionalII.label>Conventional power II</SK_ConvectionalII.label>
  <SK_ConvectionalII.description>Further advancements in power technology, give your colonists the ability to use some convectional resources fo obtaining electricity.  Unlocks the Coal Power Plant。</SK_ConvectionalII.description>


  <!-- CoalPowerPlant -->

  <SK_ConvectionalIII.label>Conventional power III</SK_ConvectionalIII.label>
  <SK_ConvectionalIII.description>Allows to build advanced power plant for refining some fuel - Fuel Power Plant。</SK_ConvectionalIII.description>


  <!-- ChemfuelPoweredGenerator
						WoodFiredGenerator -->

  <SK_PlasmaI.label>Plasma power I</SK_PlasmaI.label>
  <SK_PlasmaI.description>Allows to build advanced power plant - Tesla Lightning Generator。</SK_PlasmaI.description>


  <!-- TeslaLigthningPower -->

  <SK_PlasmaII.label>Plasma power II</SK_PlasmaII.label>
  <SK_PlasmaII.description>Open secrets of electromagnetics. Allows to build eco-friendly plasma generators。</SK_PlasmaII.description>


  <!-- PlasmaGen
								PlasmaGeothermalPlant -->

  <SK_PlasmaIII.label>Plasma power III</SK_PlasmaIII.label>
  <SK_PlasmaIII.description>Dynamic Electromagnetics allows you to fabricate advanced buildings using electromagnetic components. This unlocks the upper tier of power generation and technology found in every Glitter world installation for building Xenon-Ion Turbine。</SK_PlasmaIII.description>


  <!-- XenonIonTurbine -->

  <AirConditioning.label>Infrastructure I</AirConditioning.label>
  <AirConditioning.description>Allows you to build different Lamps, Small coolers and heaters and some Vents. Also increases battery efficiency by 15 percent。</AirConditioning.description>


  <!-- PowerSwitch
		StandingLamp
		FloorAddonA
		Cooler
		Heater
		Vent
		RH_SmallCooler
		Heater from RH -->

  <Autodoors.label>Infrastructure II</Autodoors.label>
  <Autodoors.description>Allows you to build Autodoors, Medium coolers and heaters, Utility Walls. Also increases battery efficiency by 15 percent。</Autodoors.description>


  <!-- Autodoor
						CellDoor
						ClutterFloorLampA
						CeilingLamp
						FloorLightSquare
						ClutterLampYellow -->

  <ColoredLights.label>Colored lights</ColoredLights.label>
  <ColoredLights.description>Allows colonists to construct colored lights for decorative purposes。</ColoredLights.description>

  <Batteries.label>Infrastructure III</Batteries.label>
  <Batteries.description>Allows you to build Hi-Tech Research Bench, Heavy Power Conduits, Hidden Conduits and Industrial coolers and heaters. Also increases battery efficiency by 15 percent。</Batteries.description>


  <!-- HiTechResearchBench
						EHeatedFloor
						WallLamp
						RopeLight
						Lighting_WallLight
						HiTechResearchBench
						HeavyPowerConduit
						RH_MediumHeater
						Cooler from RH
						PowerConduitInvisible -->

  <LEDTechnologyScience.label>LED Technology</LEDTechnologyScience.label>
  <LEDTechnologyScience.description>Allows the construction of more efficient lights and other buildings。</LEDTechnologyScience.description>

  <SK_InfrastructureIV.label>Infrastructure IV</SK_InfrastructureIV.label>
  <SK_InfrastructureIV.description>Allows you to build some advanced Ductwork Elements, Geothermal Heaters and Fission Batteries。</SK_InfrastructureIV.description>


  <!-- FissionBattery
								GH
								RedistHeat_IndustrialCooler
								RedistHeat_IndustrialHeater -->

  <SK_NuclearI.label>Nuclear power I</SK_NuclearI.label>
  <SK_NuclearI.description>Advanced knowledge of power generation allows you to build some Gas Centrifuge。</SK_NuclearI.description>


  <!-- GC
		CentrifugeFeeder -->

  <SK_NuclearII.label>Nuclear power II</SK_NuclearII.label>
  <SK_NuclearII.description>Geothermal power is great, except when you can't find a steam vent!  Advanced knowledge of power generation allows you to build a nuclear reactor。</SK_NuclearII.description>


</LanguageData>