<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Technology -->

  <SK_Technology.label>Technology</SK_Technology.label>
  <SK_Technology.description>Learn basic elements of survival on this harsh planet. Unlocks Grill, Fueled stove and some beds for your colonists.</SK_Technology.description>


  <!-- TableGrill
			FueledStove
			Bed
			DoubleBed -->

  <Electricity.label>Electricity</Electricity.label>
  <Electricity.description>A gateway tech into learning how to generate Electricity.</Electricity.description>

  <Fabrication.label>Production I</Fabrication.label>
  <Fabrication.description>Learn how to refine and make some useful stuff. Allows your colonists to understand the various uses of weed and tobacco, such as rolling special cigarettes, making hemp and various medicinal uses.
				\n\nAlso unlocks the candy making table to make sweet treats and Ammo Bench to create some ammo for your guns and turrets.</Fabrication.description>


  <!-- CandyMaking
			DrugLab
			AmmoBench -->

  <AdvancedFabrication.label>Production II</AdvancedFabrication.label>
  <AdvancedFabrication.description>Learn how to refine and make some useful stuff with power of electricity. Allows your colonists to create a complex coffee machine, which turns coffee beans into hot fragrant drink. You can also brew types of tea here too.
						\n\nAlso unlocks Electric Stove and Electric Brewery.</AdvancedFabrication.description>


  <!-- ElectricStove
					ElectricBrewery
					TableCoffee -->

  <Brewing.label>Brewing</Brewing.label>
  <Brewing.description>Allows you to begin brewing your own acholic drinks.</Brewing.description>


  <!-- BrewingTable -->

  <BrewingII.label>Soft Liquor</BrewingII.label>
  <BrewingII.description>Allows making of Mash for soft liqours.</BrewingII.description>

  <BrewingIII.label>Hard Liquor</BrewingIII.label>
  <BrewingIII.description>Allows making of mash for harder more complex liqours.</BrewingIII.description>

  <PackagedSurvivalMeal.label>Production III</PackagedSurvivalMeal.label>
  <PackagedSurvivalMeal.description>Advanced knowledge of how to refine and make some useful stuff with power of electricity. Learn blueprints of an Electric Pressure Cooker - a stove for canning foods, and a Professional Cook Stove - for preparing meals in bulk.</PackagedSurvivalMeal.description>


  <!-- ElectricStove_Pro
								Canningstove -->

  <BiofuelRefining.label>Сhemistry</BiofuelRefining.label>
  <BiofuelRefining.description>Allows you to use biogen opportunities. A example is making biofuel out of corn.</BiofuelRefining.description>


  <!-- TableComposter
				BioRefinery -->

  <SK_BiochemistryII.label>Biochemistry</SK_BiochemistryII.label>
  <SK_BiochemistryII.description>This allows your colonists to build the Chemical Laboratory, which can be used to create medkits and advanced prosthetic body parts.</SK_BiochemistryII.description>


  <!-- MakeCarbonAlloy
				TableChemlab -->

  <SK_Bioenergy.label>Bioenergy</SK_Bioenergy.label>
  <SK_Bioenergy.description>Learn how to refine different biomaterials into electricity. Unlocks a BioGenerator that produces electricity. Requires BioDiesel or BioMatter for a fuel source.</SK_Bioenergy.description>


  <!-- TableOrganvat -->

  <NutrientPaste.label>Food synthesizer</NutrientPaste.label>
  <NutrientPaste.description>Minor Discovery: This allows colonists to build the food synthesizer. While not the most tasty of ways to get a meal, the paste is nutritious and it does free up colonists to do other things.</NutrientPaste.description>


  <!-- NutrientPasteDispenser
								Hopper -->

  <NutrientPasteII.label>Soylent technology</NutrientPasteII.label>
  <NutrientPasteII.description>Allows you to build the Soylent Green Machine to make Soylent Green from Humanlike corpses.</NutrientPasteII.description>


  <!-- soylenttable -->

  <SK_GlassworkingI.label>Glassworking</SK_GlassworkingI.label>
  <SK_GlassworkingI.description>Making clear glass is harder than it seems but with some hard work you will find the right formula. Glass is made by a process of heating sand to a very high temperature. Unlocks Glasswork Table.</SK_GlassworkingI.description>


  <!-- GlassworkTable -->

  <SK_GlassworkingII.label>Fiberglass</SK_GlassworkingII.label>
  <SK_GlassworkingII.description>Glass is fragile but with the right tools you can make it stronger to expand the potential uses of it.</SK_GlassworkingII.description>


  <!-- DoorGlass
				TeaTable
				MakeReinforcedGlass -->

  <Prosthetics.label>Biology</Prosthetics.label>
  <Prosthetics.description>Learn basics of medicine art. Have no leg or arm, or anything else? Start to use simple prosthetics from wood and steel. To make them - build a Prosthetics Workbench.</Prosthetics.description>


  <!-- TableBasicProsthetic
				InstallArtificialPelvis
				InstallArtificialNose
				InstallSimpleProstheticFoot
				InstallSimpleProstheticHand
				InstallCrystalEye
				InstallGlassEye
				InstallSimpleProstheticArm
				InstallSimpleProstheticLeg
				InstallPegLeg
				InstallWoodenFoot
				InstallDenture
				InstallHookHand -->

  <HospitalBed.label>Hospital I</HospitalBed.label>
  <HospitalBed.description>Advanced medicine allows you to treat some simple injuries like Frostbite or Cut. Also you can install some lif esupport to your colonists and make some hospital beds.</HospitalBed.description>


  <!-- HospitalBed
				TableBasicProsthetic
				InstallLifeSupportLung
				InstallLifeSupportHeart
				InstallLifeSupportLiver
				InstallLifeSupportKidney
				InjectMedicine
				CureInjuryFrostbite
				CureInjuryScratch
				CureInjuryBite
				CureInjuryStab
				CureInjuryGunshot
				CureInjuryShredded
				CureInjuryBruise
				CureInjuryBlast
				CureInjuryCut
				CureInjuryCrack
				CureInjuryCrush
				CureInjuryBurn -->

  <VitalsMonitor.label>Hospital II</VitalsMonitor.label>
  <VitalsMonitor.description>Improvements in medical art opens new cosmettic and surgical operations. You can now install some small natural body parts like noses and ears, use artificial bones and cure gut worms, asthma, scars and deep cuts. Allows colonists to build vitals monitors which increase patients treatment quality if placed next to medical beds.</VitalsMonitor.description>


  <!-- Storage_MedicineCabinet
								VitalsMonitor
								HealScars
								InstallNaturalJaw
								CureInjurySurgicalCut
								CureChronicAsthma
								CureGutWorms
								RepairCosmeticEar
								RepairCosmeticNose
								RepairFinger
								RepairToe
								InstallArtificialBone_Small
								InstallArtificialBone_Medium
								InstallArtificialBonePiece_Large -->

  <VitalsMonitorI.label>Hospital III</VitalsMonitorI.label>
  <VitalsMonitorI.description>Improvements in medical art opens new surgical operations. You can now install some internal natural organs like heart and liver, natural body parts such as arms, legs, eyes, as well as make advanced beds specially designed to treat injured people.</VitalsMonitorI.description>


  <!-- AdvHospitalBed
								ClutterMedicKitTable
								InstallNaturalHeart
								InstallNaturalLiver
								InstallNaturalKidney
								InstallNaturalLung
								InstallNaturalEye
								InstallNaturalHeart
								InstallNaturalStomach
								InstallNaturalLeg
								InstallNaturalArm -->

  <SK_HospitalIV.label>Hospital IV</SK_HospitalIV.label>
  <SK_HospitalIV.description>Now your doctors can heal chronic diseases: Heart Artery Blockage, Muscle Parasites, Cataract, Hearing Loss, Frail and Bad Back.</SK_HospitalIV.description>


  <!-- AdvancedVitalsMonitor
										CureChronicHeartArteryBlockage
										CureChronicAlzheimers
										CureMuscleParasites
										CureChronicDementia
										CureChronicCataract
										CureChronicHearingLoss
										CureChronicFrail
										CureChronicBadBack -->

  <BrainSurgery.label>brain surgery</BrainSurgery.label>
  <BrainSurgery.description>Allows you to perform surgery on the brain.</BrainSurgery.description>

  <MedicineProduction.label>Medicine</MedicineProduction.label>
  <MedicineProduction.description>After this research you may build Medical Tables that is used to craft medicine.</MedicineProduction.description>


  <!-- meditable
				BrewMedicalDrink -->

  <SK_MedicineIII.label>Genetics</SK_MedicineIII.label>
  <SK_MedicineIII.description>Breakthrough in genetic manipulation makes it possible to construct Organ Vat, that is used to turn human corpses into biomatter and to grow natural replacement organs.</SK_MedicineIII.description>


  <!-- TableOrganvat -->

  <ComplexClothing.label>Tailoring I</ComplexClothing.label>
  <ComplexClothing.description>Learn basics of tailoring art. Unlock Tailor's Loom - a workbench equipped for tailoring basic clothing from textiles.</ComplexClothing.description>


  <!-- HandTailoringBench
		TableLoom -->

  <CarpetMaking.label>Carpet Making</CarpetMaking.label>
  <CarpetMaking.description>This allows colonists to build plush carpets that will increase the quality of their environments.</CarpetMaking.description>


  <!-- Bunch of terrain thingdefs -->

  <CarpetMakingII.label>Expert carpet making</CarpetMakingII.label>
  <CarpetMakingII.description>This allows colonists to build plush carpets that will increase the quality of their environments.</CarpetMakingII.description>

  <SterileMaterials.label>sterile materials</SterileMaterials.label>
  <SterileMaterials.description>Construct sterile tiles to make cleanrooms for safer and more effective medical treatment, research, and cooking.</SterileMaterials.description>

  <FlakArmor.label>Tailoring II</FlakArmor.label>
  <FlakArmor.description>Improvements in tailoring art opens new Electric Tailoring Bench - a workbench with a sewing machine for rapid tailoring of clothes.</FlakArmor.description>


  <!-- ElectricTailoringBench
				BenchRecycle
				MakeSynthreadCloth -->

  <PoweredArmor.label>Tailoring III</PoweredArmor.label>
  <PoweredArmor.description>Neuro-memetic robotics and advanced stein weaving technologies allow you to build the power armor and power armor helmets.</PoweredArmor.description>


  <!-- HyperTailoringBench
						MakeHyperweaveCloth -->

  <SK_ElectronicsI.label>Electronics basics</SK_ElectronicsI.label>
  <SK_ElectronicsI.description>Generate and use electricity for cooking and other simple tasks.</SK_ElectronicsI.description>


  <!-- TableElectronics -->

  <SK_TelecommunicationI.label>Telecommunication</SK_TelecommunicationI.label>
  <SK_TelecommunicationI.description>This allows colonists to construct communications station like Comms Console and Orbital Trade Beacon, so they may interact with other colonies and trade ships.</SK_TelecommunicationI.description>


  <!-- OrbitalTradeBeacon
				CommsConsole -->

  <SK_TelecommunicationII.label>Orbital Networks</SK_TelecommunicationII.label>
  <SK_TelecommunicationII.description>This research allows colonists to build Subspace Burst Transponders to contact Ships at a distance and guide them to your colony.</SK_TelecommunicationII.description>


  <!-- Buildings_SubspaceBurstTransponder -->

  <SK_TelecommunicationIII.label>Hypercomputing</SK_TelecommunicationIII.label>
  <SK_TelecommunicationIII.description>Depth of telecommunication knowledge allows colonists to build a computer terminal that provides remote access to some options of the tactical computer.</SK_TelecommunicationIII.description>


  <!-- TacticalComputer -->

  <TacticalComputerImprovedSensor.label>Improved Computer Sensors</TacticalComputerImprovedSensor.label>
  <TacticalComputerImprovedSensor.description>Improves the sensors of your tactical computer.\nThis will result in more detailed informations with many anomalies.</TacticalComputerImprovedSensor.description>

  <MicroelectronicsBasics.label>Microelectronics basics</MicroelectronicsBasics.label>
  <MicroelectronicsBasics.description>The basics of working with delicate, complex electronics. This unlocks production of Integrated Circuits and construction of Mineral Sonars - which is a device that can scan deposits in mountains to identify minerals.</MicroelectronicsBasics.description>


  <!-- MakeIntegratedCircuits
					MakeMineralSonarModule
					MobileMineralSonar -->

  <ResearchMobileMineralSonarEnhancedScan.label>Enhanced scanner</ResearchMobileMineralSonarEnhancedScan.label>
  <ResearchMobileMineralSonarEnhancedScan.description>By doing some code refactoring in the MiSoTech* noise reduction algorithms, your researchers could improve the mobile mineral sonar efficiency. Improve the MiSoTech* to enhance the mobile mineral sonar efficiency.</ResearchMobileMineralSonarEnhancedScan.description>

  <SK_ElectronicsIII.label>Nanoelectronics basics</SK_ElectronicsIII.label>
  <SK_ElectronicsIII.description>This research allows colonists to make Microchip Integrated Circuits, Life-Support device and Brain Stimulator.</SK_ElectronicsIII.description>


  <!-- makelifesupport
					MakeMicrochipIntegratedCircuits
					CreateBrainStimulator -->

  <Bionics.label>Bionics</Bionics.label>
  <Bionics.description>Discovering the concept of very small motors and circuits, new possibilities of better Synthetic internal organs prostheses and building of Synthetic Organ Assembler are now open for you.</Bionics.description>


  <!-- TableSynthetics
								MakeBioelectronicDevices
								InstallBionicHeart
								InstallBionicKidney
								InstallBionicLiver
								InstallBionicLung
								InstallBionicStomach -->

  <OrganicOptimizer.label>Organic optimization</OrganicOptimizer.label>
  <OrganicOptimizer.description>Allows you to develop nanobots to optimize and bring out the full potential of the natural body, specifically designed to aid body purists.</OrganicOptimizer.description>

  <SK_BionicsII.label>Bio engineering</SK_BionicsII.label>
  <SK_BionicsII.description>Upgrade regular bionics with BioMaterial to make them even better. Opens Bionics Workbench and different small bionic prostheses.</SK_BionicsII.description>


  <!-- TableBionics
										CreateAIChip
										InstallAdrenalineRibcage
										InstallBionicRibcage
										InstallBionicArm
										InstallBionicSpine
										InstallBionicHand
										InstallBionicFoot
										InstallBionicEar
										InstallBionicJaw -->

  <Glitterworld_Implants.label>Glitterworld implants</Glitterworld_Implants.label>
  <Glitterworld_Implants.description>Allows you to make Glitterworld implants.</Glitterworld_Implants.description>

  <SK_BionicsIII.label>Biometallurgy</SK_BionicsIII.label>
  <SK_BionicsIII.description>Breakthroughs in bionics tech and robotics allow consruction of highly advanced medical facilities.</SK_BionicsIII.description>


  <!-- UpgradingStation
												MakeRobotParts
												InstallExoskeletonSuit
												InstallAdvancedBionicSpine
												InstallAdvancedBionicJaw
												InstallAdvancedBionicEar
												InstallAdvancedBionicEye
												InstallAdvancedBionicFoot
												InstallAdvancedBionicHand
												InstallAdvancedBionicLeg
												InstallAdvancedBionicArm
												InstallAdvancedBionicArm -->

  <Stonecutting.label>Stonecutting</Stonecutting.label>
  <Stonecutting.description>Build stonecutting tables, which allow you to refine rock chunks into stone blocks that can be used for construction.</Stonecutting.description>


  <!-- TableSculpting
			TableStonecutter -->

  <SK_Quarry.label>Quarry</SK_Quarry.label>
  <SK_Quarry.description>New research in mining art allows you to build quarry - a large pit for digging up long buried resources.</SK_Quarry.description>


  <!-- QuarrySpawner -->

  <DeepDrilling.label>Geology</DeepDrilling.label>
  <DeepDrilling.description>Opens the construction of a mining and drilling rig.</DeepDrilling.description>


  <!-- Extractor
				OilExtractor
				ClayCollector -->

  <SK_Petrochemistry.label>Petrochemistry</SK_Petrochemistry.label>
  <SK_Petrochemistry.description>Enables construction of the Petrochemical Plant. This building can refine Crude Oil into usable raw materials, as well as process the materials into finished products such as Rubber and Plastic.</SK_Petrochemistry.description>


  <!-- OilRefinery
							MakeCompaste
							MakeKevlar
							MakeSyntheticFibers
							MakeCarbon -->

  <NeutroamineProduction.label>Neutroamine</NeutroamineProduction.label>
  <NeutroamineProduction.description>Produce Neutroamine from stored chemfuel, used for making medicine</NeutroamineProduction.description>

  <SynthreadProduction.label>Synthread</SynthreadProduction.label>
  <SynthreadProduction.description>Produce synthread from stored chemfuel</SynthreadProduction.description>

  <HyperweaveProduction.label>Hyperweave</HyperweaveProduction.label>
  <HyperweaveProduction.description>Discover the secrets of making Hyperweave</HyperweaveProduction.description>

  <GroundPenetratingScanner.label>Geophysics</GroundPenetratingScanner.label>
  <GroundPenetratingScanner.description>Unlocks the construction of an advanced mining station and ground penetraing scanner.</GroundPenetratingScanner.description>


  <!-- RareExtractor -->

  <OilDrilling.label>Drill for oil</OilDrilling.label>
  <OilDrilling.description>Unlocks the possibility of oil production and oil-related structures.</OilDrilling.description>

  <DeepOilWells.label>Deep Wells</DeepOilWells.label>
  <DeepOilWells.description>Drill deeper wells to access new larger oil reservoirs.</DeepOilWells.description>

  <LongRangeMineralScanner.label>long-range mineral scanner</LongRangeMineralScanner.label>
  <LongRangeMineralScanner.description>Construct long-range mineral scanners your researchers can use to detect precious minerals across the planet. Can be tuned to find a specific mineral. Requires advanced components to construct.</LongRangeMineralScanner.description>

  <Machining.label>Machining</Machining.label>
  <Machining.description>Start in researching of machining arts. Unlocks Electric Sawmill and Mending Workbench with production of mending kits for your apparel.</Machining.description>


  <!-- TableSawmillElectric
			TableMending
			MakeMendingKit -->

  <SK_MachiningII.label>Advanced machining</SK_MachiningII.label>
  <SK_MachiningII.description>Unlocks the Electric Machining Table that can process stone chunks into blocks, rubble or sand. Drill Heads can be made here. Mechanoid bodies can be disassembled here.</SK_MachiningII.description>


  <!-- TableMachining -->

  <SK_MachiningIII.label>3D Printing</SK_MachiningIII.label>
  <SK_MachiningIII.description>Unlocks the Electric Assembling Bench - an electric table for the assembling of components, wires, mechanisms, and advanced mechanisms and basic hand tools.</SK_MachiningIII.description>


  <!-- AdvToolBench
							MakeAdvMechanism_Hand
							MakeAdvMechanism_Electric -->

  <TransportPod.label>Transportation</TransportPod.label>
  <TransportPod.description>Construct launchable transport pods that you can use to launch people and supplies long distances across the planet's surface.</TransportPod.description>

  <SK_AppliedPhysicsI.label>Exotic Matter</SK_AppliedPhysicsI.label>
  <SK_AppliedPhysicsI.description>Unlocks the Inorganic Matter Converter - a converter to turn resources into inorganic matter. Inorganic matter can be used to make other resources.</SK_AppliedPhysicsI.description>


  <!-- MatterConverter -->

  <SK_Robotics.label>Robotics</SK_Robotics.label>
  <SK_Robotics.description>Allows you to build small robots for simple tasks such as cleaning and hauling.</SK_Robotics.description>


  <!-- RobAssem
											MakeHexcell
											AIRobot_RechargeStation_Cleaner
											AIRobot_RechargeStation_Hauler -->

  <SK_NanotechnologyI.label>Nanotechnology</SK_NanotechnologyI.label>
  <SK_NanotechnologyI.description>Research how to expand your storage capabilities. Allows you to build a specialized storage. Each nano storage can hold up to ten items.</SK_NanotechnologyI.description>


  <!-- NanoStorage -->

  <Cryptosleep.label>cryptosleep casket</Cryptosleep.label>
  <Cryptosleep.description>Construct cryptosleep caskets, which can put living beings in a state of indefinite suspended animation.</Cryptosleep.description>


  <!-- Disabled. Nanoprinter still not updated to 1.0
												
														  <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="HitechLabStationBase">
															<defName>SK_NanotechnologyII</defName>
															<label>NanoReplication</label>
															<description>Research how to modify your nano bots to replicate objects. Allows you to build a nano printer. It has the capability to replicate scanned items. Also unlocks Nano Scanner that allows the nano printer to scan the internal structure of objects.</description>
															<baseCost>4500</baseCost>
															<techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
															<tab>SpacerTech</tab>
															<researchViewX>3.77</researchViewX>
															<researchViewY>2.01</researchViewY>
																<prerequisites>
																	<li>SK_NanotechnologyI</li>
																</prerequisites>
														  </ResearchProjectDef> -->

  <SK_Cybernetics.label>Cybernetics</SK_Cybernetics.label>
  <SK_Cybernetics.description>Allows you to create new cybernetics body parts in a Chemical Laboratory.</SK_Cybernetics.description>


  <!-- CreateGTHeart
																	CreateGTKidney
																	CreateGTLiver
																	CreateGTStomach
																	CreateGTLung
																	CreateGTBionicSpine
																	CreateGTBionicEar
																	CreateGTBionicJaw
																	CreateGTBionicLeg
																	CreateGTBionicFoot
																	CreateGTBionicHand
																	CreateGTBionicArm
																	CreateGTBionicEye
																	InstallGTSpine
																	InstallGTDentures
																	InstallGTStomach
																	InstallGTLiver
																	InstallGTKidney
																	InstallGTLung
																	InstallGTHeart
																	InstallGTFoot
																	InstallArchotechLeg
																	InstallGTHand
																	InstallArchotechArm
																	InstallArchotechEye
																	InstallGTEar
																	UpgradingStation -->

  <SK_DermalRegenerator.label>Dermal regenerator</SK_DermalRegenerator.label>
  <SK_DermalRegenerator.description>Allows construction of the Dermal Regenerator. This is a medical device that is able to scan and repair surface tissue scars.</SK_DermalRegenerator.description>


  <!-- DermalRegenerator -->

  <Personal_Shield_research.label>Nanite shielding</Personal_Shield_research.label>
  <Personal_Shield_research.description>Using nano technology Nanites have been developed that can be implanted in colonists to heal them or protect them from damage. Unfortunately due to the limited power and size of the Nanites they must be replaced from the Colonist Upgrade Station after each use.</Personal_Shield_research.description>


  <!-- <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="IndustrialBase">
																	<defName>SK_MindAlteringDevice</defName>
																	<label>Mind Altering Device</label>
																	
																	<baseCost>2200</baseCost>
																	<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
																		<prerequisites>
																			<li>SK_NanotechnologyII</li>
																		</prerequisites>
																  </ResearchProjectDef> -->

  <SK_AppliedPhysicsII.label>Quantum mechanics</SK_AppliedPhysicsII.label>
  <SK_AppliedPhysicsII.description>Unlocks Hadron Collider - an apparatus for accelerating subatomic particles to high velocities by means of electric or electromagnetic fields. The accelerated particles are generally made to collide with other particles, either as a research technique or for the generation of high-energy X-rays and gamma rays.</SK_AppliedPhysicsII.description>


  <!-- HadronCollider
											HadronColliderFeeder -->

  <SK_Antimatter.label>Antimatter</SK_Antimatter.label>
  <SK_Antimatter.description>The antimatter contained separate from the normal matter by magnetic fields so that no unintended reactions take place. The energy would then be extracted in much the same way that nuclear reactors capture the expended heat and light energy from fission reactions.</SK_Antimatter.description>


  <!-- AntimatterReactor -->

  <SK_AppliedPhysicsIII.label>Alien Materials</SK_AppliedPhysicsIII.label>
  <SK_AppliedPhysicsIII.description>Advanced factorization the step in understanding the basics of advanced manufacturing methods, to give your colony access to the latest assembly machinery.</SK_AppliedPhysicsIII.description>


  <!-- Matterfab
													ImpactionCharge -->

  <SK_Teleportation.label>Stargate</SK_Teleportation.label>
  <SK_Teleportation.description>By studying the symbols on the device you have discovered and cross-referencing with stellar constellations you have found out how to activate it and travel to other locations.</SK_Teleportation.description>

  <ShieldAssembly.label>orbital shield generator</ShieldAssembly.label>
  <ShieldAssembly.description>Allows you to build the Shield Generator, which prevents orbital bombardment.</ShieldAssembly.description>

  <ShipBasics.label>Austronautics</ShipBasics.label>
  <ShipBasics.description>Allows you to start researching more advanced shipbuilding technologies and eventually build a ship to escape the planet.</ShipBasics.description>


  <!-- Ship_Beam -->

  <ShipSensorCluster.label>ship sensor cluster</ShipSensorCluster.label>
  <ShipSensorCluster.description>Allows you to construct long-range sensors for a ship.</ShipSensorCluster.description>


  <!-- Ship_CryptosleepCasket -->

  <ShipCryptosleep.label>Spaceship caskets</ShipCryptosleep.label>
  <ShipCryptosleep.description>Allows you to construct ship cryptosleep caskets for transporting cryptosleeping colonists between the stars.</ShipCryptosleep.description>

  <ShipEngine.label>Spaceship antimatter propulsion</ShipEngine.label>
  <ShipEngine.description>Allows you to use an antimatter containment core to construct an antimatter drive for a ship.</ShipEngine.description>


  <!-- Ship_Engine -->

  <ShipReactor.label>Spaceship antimatter reactor</ShipReactor.label>
  <ShipReactor.description>Allows you to use an antimatter containment core to build a working antimatter reactor to power a ship.</ShipReactor.description>


  <!-- Ship_Reactor -->

  <ShipComputerCore.label>Spaceship computer core</ShipComputerCore.label>
  <ShipComputerCore.description>Allows coercing an existing AI persona into a usable AI computer core for ship guidance.</ShipComputerCore.description>


  <!-- Ship_ComputerCore -->

  <Smithing.label>Smithing</Smithing.label>
  <Smithing.description>Build smithies for crafting metal weapons and tools.</Smithing.description>


  <!-- FueledSmithy -->

  <LongBlades.label>Weapon smithing</LongBlades.label>
  <LongBlades.description>Learn how to craft powerful swords and spears.</LongBlades.description>

  <Greatbow.label>Throwing weapons</Greatbow.label>
  <Greatbow.description>Learn to craft powerful bows and crossbows.</Greatbow.description>

  <Gunsmithing.label>Metalworking</Gunsmithing.label>
  <Gunsmithing.description>Learn how to build electric smithy and Weapon Crafting Workbench.\n\nThe electric smithy allows smithing items without fuel. The Weapon Crafting Workbench produces ranged weapons like pistols and rifles. Can smelt weapons down into metal.</Gunsmithing.description>


  <!-- ElectricSmithy
					WeaponCraftingWorkTable -->

  <BlowbackOperation.label>Advanced metalworking</BlowbackOperation.label>
  <BlowbackOperation.description>Learn how to construct Advanced Weapon Crafting Workbench that produces advanced ranged weapons like military assault rifles, missile launchers and heavy machine guns.</BlowbackOperation.description>


  <!-- AdvWeaponCraftingWorkTable -->

  <PrecisionRifling.label>Hightech metalworking</PrecisionRifling.label>
  <PrecisionRifling.description>Learn now to build Mechanoid Weapon Workbench that produces futuristic Mechanoid weapons, such as laser beam rifles.</PrecisionRifling.description>


  <!-- MechWeaponCraftingWorkTable -->

  <ElectricSmelting.label>Metallurgy</ElectricSmelting.label>
  <ElectricSmelting.description>Learn how to build electric smelters. The electric smelters uses heat and strong electromagnets to extract useful metal from slag chunks and other items.</ElectricSmelting.description>


  <!-- ElectricSmelter
					MakeSilverBars_Electric
					MakeCopperBars_Electric
					MakeGoldBars_Electric
					MakeSteelBars_Electric
					MakeBronze_Electric -->

  <PlateArmor.label>Casting</PlateArmor.label>
  <PlateArmor.description>Learn how to prepare different metals like Aluminium, Cupronicke, Ferromanganese and Ferrosilicon.</PlateArmor.description>


  <!-- MakeAluminiumBars_Electric
					MakeCupronickelAlloy
					MakeFerrosiliconAlloy -->

  <SK_MetallurgyIII.label>Thermodynamics</SK_MetallurgyIII.label>
  <SK_MetallurgyIII.description>Metal Fabrication allows us to work with hitech alloys. Specifically using complex materials like Ferronickel, CobaltIron, Alnico and Nichrome.</SK_MetallurgyIII.description>


  <!-- ProcessNickelOre
							ProcessForChromium
							MakeFerronickelAlloy
							EAF
							MakeAlnicoAlloy -->

  <SK_MetallurgyIV.label>Nano metallurgy</SK_MetallurgyIV.label>
  <SK_MetallurgyIV.description>Depths of metallurgy art unlocks new recipes for EAP like Titanium, Tungsten, Stellite, Ferrotitanium, Nitino and Pobedite.</SK_MetallurgyIV.description>


  <!-- ProcessTitanium
									ProcessTungsten
									MakeStelliteAlloy
									MakeFerrotitaniumAlloy
									MakeNitinolAlloy
									MakePobediteAlloy -->

  <SK_ConstructionI.label>Construction I</SK_ConstructionI.label>
  <SK_ConstructionI.description>Learn the basics of putting the raw materials of this planet to good use.  This technology unlocks the ability to construct robust structures using metal bars and stone blocks. Also unlocks roofs construction and Hand Concrete Mixer.</SK_ConstructionI.description>


  <!-- ConcreteMixer
		Column -->

  <SK_ConstructionII.label>Construction II</SK_ConstructionII.label>
  <SK_ConstructionII.description>Further advancements in construction, unlock Electric Concrete Mixer.  
					Also unlocks Motion Sensor Lighted Wall to light up your colonists along their merry way.</SK_ConstructionII.description>


  <!-- EConcreteMixer
					WallLighted
					RDoor -->

  <SK_ConstructionIII.label>Construction III</SK_ConstructionIII.label>
  <SK_ConstructionIII.description>Nothing says keep out like a steel reinforced door blocking your way. Continued advancement in construction unlocks the ability to secure your base with blast doors.</SK_ConstructionIII.description>


</LanguageData>